

Hoang Do

Technical Leader

About Me

Hello! I am Hoang Do. I am passionate about web development. I am a skilled Back-end Developer, and I am familiar with web frameworks such as PHP-Laravel, Node-Express/NestJs or Java-Spring. I also have experience with Front-end frameworks like React, Angular, and VueJS.

I'm also have experience with Technical Leaders and Software Architect roles, and familiar with maintain, optimization, design systems, research, training members as a Technical Leaders.

DOB 02/01/1994

Email hoangdo.2194@gmail.com

Phone +84 35 537 4643

Address Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Professional Skills

- Design web systems using PHP/Laravel, Java-Spring, NodeJs-Nest as backend. React/Angular as frontend
- Design microservices system using knowledge about the backend systems, combine with protocols like queue, message brokers, grpc, http,...
- Design high performance databases using Sql (Mysql, Postgresql,...)
- Standardizing code writing, using knowledge about clean code, such as Design Pattern, SOLID, Domain Driven Design,...
- Optimize system performance, using Sql indexes, partition, Elasticsearch, Caching,... or redesign some modules.
- Containerization using docker, docker compose,...
- Researching and conveying new technologies to the development team.
- Researching and identifying existing issues in the system and finding solutions.
- Researching and seeking technological solutions to address user pain points.

Work Experience

Technical Leader at TopCV Viet Nam

Jun, 2021 - Present

TopCV ERP

- Role: Technical Leaders.
- Team size: 10.
- Product Descriptions: Provide solution and tools to operate sale business, such as: products, kpi, sale, payment, leads, customer support,....

TopCV Internal Operating System

- Role: Technical Leaders.
- Team size: 10.
- Product Descriptions: Provide features about HRM and Workflow operation, some features are: workflow, departments, salary tables,...

Software Architect at TopCV Viet Nam

- Role: SA.
- Team size: 2.
- Research and optimize systems, to reduce cost of cloud services.
- Optimize using knowledge about databases, caching, search engines, prebuilt data,...

Web Developer at Amit Group

September, 2018 - January, 2021

- Designed systems and databases according to customers' requirements, developed and maintained the backend and frontend applications (admin sites) for most projects.
- Performed a full life-cycle of developing and deploying products.

Education

Bachelor in Software Engineering from FPT

University

2022 - Present

Get a higher education to obtain the Bachelor's Degree.

Higher diploma in Software Engineering from

FPT Aptech

2017 - 2019

Took this course to get the basics of becoming a developer.

Projects

React hook guard the open source

2021

Successfully built a routing and guarding library for Reactjs based on React-Router-dom 5 after three months of working with React and the original react-router-dom library. It helps my colleagues and me control the routing easily with multiple layouts, authentication, and authorization features of React app.

tindohanghieu.com

2019

A web system provides products from high-end brands, where peole can trade or buy popular items.

- Main functions: Social, Chat, Live Stream.
- Responsibilities: Systems design, Backend developer & Frontend developer (admin site), interface intergration, and deployment.
- Language Framework: PHP (Laravel), Mysql, NodeJs (NestJs Framework), Angular.
- Coverage: Backend ~ 70% Frontend ~ 50% (Admin site).

Hoang Cong Car

2018 - 2019

Hoang Cong is a domestic privatized transportation company where customers can easily get a one-way/ round trip by

themselves.

- Main functions: Ticket booking, Trip management,...
- Responsibilities: Systems design, Backend developer, Frontend developer (admin site), and deployment.
- Language Framework: PHP (Laravel), MySql, Angular, VueJs.
- Coverage: Backend ~ 90% Frontend ~ 80% (Admin site).

Various Projects at TopCV and Amit Group

2018 - present

Have been developing and maintaining various projects for both TopCV and Amit Group such as the TopCV's website (topcv.vn) and TopCV's internal systems, <u>E-Caf by Pan United</u> using Spring Boot - Java, and <u>tangthuvien.vn</u>, TopCV internal operation systems, TopCV ERP...

Contact

Address

Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Phone

+84 35 537 4643

Email

hoangdo.2194@gmail.com

A

https://www.facebook.com/hoangdo.2194

(0)

https://www.instagram.com/hoangdo.2194

https://github.com/aaaahoang123